<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF>8"?>
<?xml>stylesheet href="hide>it.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>
 
<layouttype></layouttype>

<item>
<title>A Bad Moms Christmas</title>
<summary>Storyline
A Bad Moms Christmas follows our three under-appreciated and over-burdened women as they rebel against the challenges and expectations of the Super Bowl for moms: Christmas. And as if creating a more perfect holiday for their families wasn't hard enough, they must do all of that while hosting and entertaining their own mothers. By the end of the journey, our moms will redefine how to make the holidays special for all and discover a closer relationship with their mothers.
15 | 1h 44min | Adventure , Comedy | 1 November 2017</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/sg5e9wto99jx</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTUwNTA4MDMxNl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMjE4NjQ0MzI@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTY0NjgyMTExOV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNDY0NDU3MjI@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,1515,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>A Charlie Brown Christmas</title>
<summary>Storyline
When Charlie Brown complains about the overwhelming materialism that he sees amongst everyone during the Christmas season, Lucy suggests that he become director of the school Christmas paegent. Charlie Brown accepts, but it proves to be a frustrating struggle. When an attempt to restore the proper spirit with a forlorn little fir Christmas tree fails, he needs Linus' help to learn what the real meaning of Christmas is.
U | 25min | Animation , Comedy , Family | TV Movie 9 December 1965</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/nipji8i20i7a</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTQ1NDQxNTcxN15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNzY1Njc1MzE@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjdlMWVmNzYtMzQwMy00MzQxLThhYzktZDMwMmNiMTMxNTYyXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNDU4MDA0NTM@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>A Christmas Carol (1938)</title>
<summary>Storyline
On Christmas Eve, an old miser named Ebenezer Scrooge is visited by the spirit of his former partner, Jacob Marley. The deceased partner was in his lifetime as mean and miserly as Scrooge is now and he warns him to change his ways or face the consequences in the afterlife. Scrooge dismisses the apparition but the first of the three ghosts, the Ghost of Christmas Past, visits as promised. Scrooge sees those events in his past life, both happy and sad, that forged his character. The second spirit, the Ghost of Christmas Present, shows him how many currently celebrate Christmas. The Ghost of Christmas yet to Come shows him how he will be remembered once he is gone. To his delight, the spirits complete their visits in one night giving him the opportunity to mend his ways.
U | 1h 9min | Drama , Family , Fantasy | 16 December 1938</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/hwgp4bpmqkp1</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTQyY2Q0YjktNDFhZS00N2FkLTk1MDAtNjRkYTMwMWM0M2YzXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMDUyOTUyNQ@@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTc5MTIzOTQ0M15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwOTYzMzkwNw@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,1253,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>A Christmas Carol</title>
<summary>Storyline
Miser Ebenezer Scrooge is awakened on Christmas Eve by spirits who reveal to him his own miserable existence, what opportunities he wasted in his youth, his current cruelties, and the dire fate that awaits him if he does not change his ways. Scrooge is faced with his own story of growing bitterness and meanness, and must decide what his own future will hold: death or redemption.
PG | 1h 36min | Animation , Drama , Family | 4 November 2009</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/a6e5sygvw3dr</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTM1MTI5ODU4MV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNTYyNTU4Mg@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,676,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTgwOTU3NDYwMl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMTcxODg4Mg@@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,749_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>A Christmas Eve Miracle</title>
<summary>Storyline
Sharon and Dustin Holden (Olivia D'abo and Anthony Starke) were High School sweethearts. They went to the same college and graduate school together and earned everything they ever dreamed of: great kids, great jobs, and the loyal golden retriever, "Jerry" (Jon Voight). But before long, Sharons's career consumes her world. In an effort to rekindle the joyous family life they once shared, Dustin insists on taking a Christmas vacation to their old stomping grounds, Farthering Pines. When they arrive, they're greeted by Jack Carter (C. Thomas Howell), Robert Jones (Jonathan Silverman) and their families. Despite the festivities, Sharon just can't seem to pull herself away from her work. Frustrated in juggling both her family and work life, Sharon wonders aloud how life would be if she and Dustin did not have children. The next day she wakes up to find that her wish has come true and her children are nowhere to be seen! At first she enjoys this new version of her life, but upon seeing how happy the Jones and Carter families are, she recognizes this isn't the life she wants. Can Sharon find a way to get her family back? Will she realize the true meaning of Christmas? Will the Holden family reunite before the clock strikes midnight?
1h 20min | Comedy , Family | 1 December 2015</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/hb0cb2imz861</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTE0MjEwOTUzMzBeQTJeQWpwZ15BbWU4MDQzMTM4Mzcx._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTE0MjEwOTUzMzBeQTJeQWpwZ15BbWU4MDQzMTM4Mzcx._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>A Christmas Horror Story</title>
<summary>Storyline
High school students investigate a mysterious homicide that occurred the prior holiday season, a couple notices their young son is acting strangely after a snowy forest trip to cut down a traditional tree and one family are stalked through a winter wonderland by Krampus, the Xmas demon. Meanwhile at the North Pole, Santa is fending off zombie elves.
15 | 1h 39min | Fantasy , Horror , Mystery | 2 October 2015</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/wjciwbxvu5fj</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BODg3NTAwNzk5M15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNjA4OTE3MDI@._V1_SX677_CR0,0,677,999_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTE0NDY4NDAxNjNeQTJeQWpwZ15BbWU4MDQ1NzgyNDcx._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,1333,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>A Christmas Star</title>
<summary>Storyline
Born under the Christmas Star, Noelle believes she has the gift to perform miracles, so when conniving developer McKerrod threatens her peaceful life she and her friends determine to use this gift to thwart his plans and save their village.
U | 1h 22min | Family | 13 May 2017</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/styoku2nms2g</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNjcxMDU4ODg5N15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwODc2MjU5OTE@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTU3NjQ1MzcwNF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNTk5NTg2NTE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,851,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>A Christmas Story</title>
<summary>Storyline
Christmas is approaching and 9 year-old Ralphie wants only one thing: a Red Ryder Range 200 Shot BB gun. When he mentions it at the dinner table, his mother's immediate reaction is that he'll shoot his eye out. He then decides on a perfect theme for his teacher but her reaction is like his. He fantasizes about what it would be like to be Red Ryder and catch the bad guys. When the big day arrives he gets lots of present under the tree including a lovely gift from his aunt that his mother just adores. But what about the BB gun?
PG | 1h 34min | Comedy , Family | 26 October 1984</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/nzuxbt8701ym</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BOWMyNjE0MzEtMzVjNy00NjIxLTg0ZjMtMWJhNGI1YmVjYTczL2ltYWdlXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNzc5MjA3OA@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,656,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMmZkMzMyYTItZmU2MS00ZGUwLWJiNDAtNDQ4MDA5NmNiY2MzXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNDU4MDA0NTM@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>A Firehouse Christmas</title>
<summary>Storyline
Firefighter Jenny has fallen in love with Tom. However his ex-wife Mary (a bestselling author) demands a reconciliation if he wants to see his daughter at Christmas.
1h 28min | Drama , Romance | TV Movie 15 December 2016</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/m3cuvjkpomph</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNGEwNDRjZjgtYzFiYy00MDZhLWJkYTktMzNjZDVlOGU5ZDM0L2ltYWdlL2ltYWdlXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMjAzMjcxNTE@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNGEwNDRjZjgtYzFiYy00MDZhLWJkYTktMzNjZDVlOGU5ZDM0L2ltYWdlL2ltYWdlXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMjAzMjcxNTE@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>All I Want for Christmas</title>
<summary>Storyline
When a boy's Christmas wish of having different parents comes true, he finds himself living the extravagant lifestyle he always dreamed of... But at what cost?
PG | 1h 26min | Comedy , Family | TV Movie 30 November 2014</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/ee31o8yx8ui7</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTczODcxODk1Ml5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNzI0NjcxNzE@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTczODcxODk1Ml5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNzI0NjcxNzE@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>All I Want for Christmas Is You</title>
<summary>Storyline
The film centers on young Mariah, a little girl who dreams of getting a dog for Christmas year after year. This Christmas her dream is fueled after seeing a puppy named Princess at the local pet store. To see if she's ready for the responsibility, Mariah is tasked with dog-sitting her uncle's crazy canine Jack, who upends the family's holiday preparations with his various shenanigans.
U | 1h 31min | Animation , Comedy , Family | Video 13 November 2017</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/9ynvh9tq8cir</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BY2ExY2NlNDEtMzg4ZS00MmQ1LWE2MzgtYmIwODJiNDUwYWY1XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTUzNjcwOTM@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZDgzMjgxNTgtZDFkYi00NDRiLWI2MTQtNDc2MmY0Nzk1NjgyXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyODEyMzI2OTE@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,914_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Almost Christmas</title>
<summary>Storyline
Walter Meyer (Danny Glover) is a retired mechanic who lost the love of his life almost a year ago. For the holidays, he invites his now grown children and their families to his house (where they all grew up) for a traditional celebration. Walter soon realizes that if his bickering children and the rest of the family can spend five days together under the same roof, it will truly be a Christmas miracle.
12A | 1h 51min | Comedy , Drama | 25 November 2016</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/khowb3a6ap1f</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjM1MTkwNTQ1Ml5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNTc5ODgxOTE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,631,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTU0Njk2Njg0M15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwODM2NDI2ODE@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,866_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Alone for Christmas</title>
<summary>Storyline
When a family visits Grandma's house on Christmas Eve, they leave their dog at home alone. And when burglars try to take the presents from under the tree, the dog must use every trick it knows to stop them.
PG | 1h 27min | Action , Comedy , Family | Video 15 October 2013</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/o8vh4lwtj85b</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTQ0MTM2NDI3M15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMTEzNjg4MDE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,713,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTQ0MTM2NDI3M15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMTEzNjg4MDE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,713,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>A Merry Friggin' Christmas</title>
<summary>Storyline
Boyd Mitchler and his family must spend Christmas with his estranged family of misfits. Upon realizing that he left all his son's gifts at home, he hits the road with his dad in an attempt to make the 8-hour round trip before sunrise.
15 | 1h 28min | Comedy | 22 November 2014</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/hliye6n4sve4</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTk1NDQ4MzE4Nl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNTU2NjY5MjE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,692,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTk1NDQ4MzE4Nl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNTU2NjY5MjE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,692,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Angel of Christmas</title>
<summary>Storyline
Susan gets a chance at her first real article, writing about the family angel, which were handcrafted by her great-grandfather. It is said to have a history of bringing people together. Working hard to get the article done on time, she is torn between the handsome, successful Derek and the free-spirited artist Brady. A well-crafted, feel-good christmas movie.
1h 24min | Comedy , Romance | TV Movie 29 November 2015</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/snprw1f9jjq9</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNjJlMGI5ZjUtZTRlMS00NzkzLTk3YWMtY2Q0YjZiZmE1N2Y5XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjE4MjY2MDg@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,699,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZTNmODJlNDAtZTk2MS00MjI0LTlmOGMtNzdlMzZmMTg1NWZlXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTIxOTk5MzY@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>A Puppy for Christmas</title>
<summary>Storyline
After adopting a cute puppy, Noelle's world is turned upside down when her boyfriend breaks up with her. After accepting an invitation to spend the holidays with a co-worker, she is surrounded by the Christmas cheer of a happy family and soon sparks begin to fly.
1h 25min | Drama | TV Movie 25 November 2016</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/fu9fz0j4lpxx</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMDRjYmY3MDAtZTlmOS00ODAxLTlmMWQtZDJlNjBlOTU2M2E5XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTM3MDMyMDQ@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNTFiODZhYmItNmM5OC00YWMzLWI5MGUtODllYjU2OGZlYmIzL2ltYWdlL2ltYWdlXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNzk0NTA5NQ@@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>A Royal Christmas</title>
<summary>Storyline
Prince Leopold, heir of queen Isadora of Cordinia (a fictitious cheap Monaco version), enjoyed studying incognito in Philadelphia and shocks his mother by bringing home a lasting souvenir: Yankee seamstress and would be-designer Emily Taylor, to whom he proposed just before unveiling his royal identity. Isidora is hell-bent on chasing the commoner intruder and marrying Leo off to an eager, overconfident aristocratic youth friend, Natasha, Duchess of Warren. Leopold, the devoted palace butler Victor and his staff are rather pleased with Emily and her fast progress in society manners, but Isidora won't give up until she breaks Leopold's heart.
1h 30min | Comedy , Family , Romance | TV Movie 21 November 2014</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/henu3af4f2rn</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZTMxZDRmZDEtY2NhZC00ZWEzLWI4NDUtMjQzZjQ5N2E4YjQ0XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNDIyMTQ3Ng@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,708,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZTMxZDRmZDEtY2NhZC00ZWEzLWI4NDUtMjQzZjQ5N2E4YjQ0XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNDIyMTQ3Ng@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,708,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Arthur Christmas</title>
<summary>Storyline
Arthur Christmas reveals the incredible, never-before seen answer to every child's question: 'So how does Santa deliver all those presents in one night?' The answer: Santa's exhilarating, ultra-high-tech operation hidden beneath the North Pole. But at the center of the film is a story about a family in a state of comic dysfunction and an unlikely hero, Arthur, with an urgent mission that must be completed before Christmas morning dawns.
U | 1h 37min | Animation , Adventure , Comedy | 11 November 2011</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/0h8u7idupghg</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTYyMjMyMzEzMl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMDg4NTM5Ng@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,675,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjA5MTg1Mzg2N15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMjg0NDczNDM@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>A Very Harold & Kumar Christmas</title>
<summary>Storyline
Six years have elapsed since Guantanemo Bay, leaving Harold and Kumar estranged from one another with very different families, friends and lives. But when Kumar arrives on Harold's doorstep during the holiday season with a mysterious package in hand, he inadvertently burns down Harold's father-in-law's beloved Christmas tree. To fix the problem, Harold and Kumar embark on a mission through New York City to find the perfect Christmas tree, once again stumbling into trouble at every single turn.
18 | 1h 30min | Adventure , Comedy | 9 December 2011</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/1p2fkaos06vi</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTY3MjQ3NTEyNV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNzI0ODcyNg@@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTY3MjQ3NTEyNV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNzI0ODcyNg@@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>A Very Murray Christmas</title>
<summary>Storyline
Murray, playing himself, trying to avoid a Hollywood figure who wants to represent the actor, who famously forgoes having a manager or agent. And somewhere in there will be rooms for Christmas carols to be sung by the actors (everyone is playing themselves) and probably more bits and pieces of holiday cheer.
12 | 56min | Comedy , Music , Musical | TV Special 4 December 2015</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/90fqscydi9t7</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTY3MDI2NjAzMl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNDY4NDgyNzE@._V1_SY1000_SX676_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>http://shabier.com/wallpapers/red-christmas-wallpaper/red-christmas-wallpaper_265124.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Bad Santa</title>
<summary>Storyline
Willie T. Stokes is a convicted con man who's led a miserable life. He drinks heavily and constantly embarrasses himself publicly. He only works once a year dressed as Santa. But then come Christmas Eve, he and his pint-sized helper dwarf Marcus stage elaborate robberies and take their department stores for everything they got. This time around, Willie gets distracted by large women, a bartender who is attracted to Santas, and a kid who's convinced he's the real deal. However, Marcus must once again put up with Willie's heavy drinking and a series of incidents that constantly shoot themselves in the foot. Will Willie and Marcus make it to next Christmas? Or will this be the year the dynamic duo finally face justice?
15 | 1h 31min | Comedy , Crime , Drama | 5 November 2004</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/y5uxtc42ryw6</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjA4Njg1MDcwN15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTYwMzAxNjM3._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjAyOTYwNDk3N15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTYwODExNjM3._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Bad Santa 2</title>
<summary>Storyline
It's the most wonderful time of the year again, and the not-in-the-slightest reformed safe-cracker Willie Soke is breathing the air of freedom once more, failing miserably to keep himself afloat thirteen whole years after his last achievements. Still addicted to alcohol and at the end of his tether, Soke will reluctantly accept his former sidekick Marcus' truce and his daring plan for another Yuletide caper--this time targeting a Chicago charity on Christmas Eve. However, as Willie slips back into his Santa's red suit again, much to his disappointment, he will discover that another partner in crime is also eager to join in the heist: his desperate for cash estranged mother, Sunny. Can Willie work around his mummy issues, especially now that the closest thing to family, Thurman Merman, comes to town for a visit?
15 | 1h 32min | Comedy , Crime , Drama | 23 November 2016</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/a0jcentzt6yh</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjM2MjE5Mzc4OF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMjc3NjEyMDI@._V1_SY1000_SX675_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYjg1NmEyZjItMTEzNy00NGQ5LTgyZGItY2JhYzRjOWIwMzZiXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNDE5MTU2MDE@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Barbie in 'A Christmas Carol'</title>
<summary>Storyline
Barbie stars in her first holiday movie in this heart-warming adaptation of the classic Dickens story filled with cherished Christmas carols, fabulous fashions and lots of laughs!
1h 16min | Animation , Family | Video 23 October 2008</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/mbz9ukhdg9cz</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTQ0ODEzMTcwM15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNzM5MjA2MDE@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNWJiMmQ0MGYtNDhmNC00ZTBmLTg5YzktNDYwY2EzYTJmNzI0XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNDgyODgxNjE@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Barbie: A Perfect Christmas</title>
<summary>Storyline
Barbie and her sisters have a whirlwind of activity as they pack and prepare for their big trip to Manhattan, It's December 23rd, where they're going to have The Perfect Christmas! Mom and Dad are already in the city for work, so it'll be wonderful to meet them there for the holiday.
1h 14min | Animation , Family | Video 16 November 2011</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/xxe6f4vfs9ow</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTEwNjU5NzE3NDheQTJeQWpwZ15BbWU4MDUxMzYwNjAx._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTRjODU1NWEtZGVkOS00MmZkLTkwNmEtNTgwNjVkMDNmYmRlXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNDgyODgxNjE@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Black Christmas</title>
<summary>Storyline
In the 70's, the boy Billy is born with yellow skin due to a liver disease and his dysfunctional mother rejects him. Later he witnesses his mother and her lover killing his beloved father and burying him in the basement of their house, and he is locked in the attic alone along his childhood. When he is a teenager, he is sexually abused by his mother and she has a baby girl called Agnes. During Christmas, the deranged Billy escapes from his imprisonment, kills his mother and stepfather and blinds one eye of Agnes. He is declared insane and his sister is sent to an orphanage. In the present days, Billy escapes from the Clark Sanatorium to spend Christmas with his family. Meanwhile, his former house is the Delta Alpha Kappa sorority house in the campus of the Clement University, and the housemother and the sisters Kelli Presley, Dana, Lauren Hannon, Megan, Heather, Megan Helms, Melissa and Eve Agnew are preparing the house for Christmas party in a stormy night while Clair Crosby is in her room writing a card to bury the hatchet with her sister. When three sisters vanish, the others receive weird phone calls and believe something is wrong, but they find that they are trapped in the location.
15 | 1h 24min | Horror | 15 December 2006</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/lx1z1a8xsgej</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTY0NDQzODE2OV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNjQ4ODE3MDI@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,677,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BODk0NzgyZDQtZGNmNy00YjUxLWI5ZDAtM2RmZWI0OGQzZjUwXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjQ4ODE4MzQ@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Christmas Bounty</title>
<summary>Storyline
A former bounty hunter turns into an elementary schoolteacher. Determined to have a normal life and keep her bounty hunter past a secret, she reluctantly returns home for Christmas to help save the family business by catching the one bounty that got away. But when her fiancé follows her home for the holiday, she struggles to hide her wild family business and a bounty hunter ex-boyfriend she thought she'd left behind.
1h 30min | Action , Comedy | TV Movie 26 November 2013</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/x9xtw58a05zi</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTQ1NTQ1NjQ5Ml5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMTQwNjU0MDE@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTQ5NjgzNTY2Ml5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMDE3Mzk3MDE@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Christmas Cupid</title>
<summary>Storyline
Sloane is a beautiful, stylish woman on the fast track to success in her public relations firm when a starlet client, Caitlin, dies. Caitlin immediately becomes Sloane's own personal "Jacob Marley" (the Christmas Carol ghost) ushering in the spirits of Christmas past, present, and future - all in the guises of Sloane's former boyfriends. Sloane finds out first hand that her unethical ways and workaholic habits need to change and that reuniting with one of the past lovers whom she jilted may be the answer for a happy-ever-after life.
1h 25min | Comedy , Family , Fantasy | TV Movie 12 December 2010</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/lk3lcqp53ol3</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZWFkMzM5YTctY2Y1YS00MzhlLTg4MjktYmJhYTkxNTk5OTNiL2ltYWdlXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTM3MDMyMDQ@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZWFkMzM5YTctY2Y1YS00MzhlLTg4MjktYmJhYTkxNTk5OTNiL2ltYWdlXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTM3MDMyMDQ@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Christmas Eve</title>
<summary>Storyline
"Christmas Eve" is the dramatic, comedic story of six different groups of New Yorkers who get stuck inside elevators overnight on Christmas Eve. With nowhere to go and no one to interact with but each other, all of them are transformed by the events of their long night together.
PG | 1h 35min | Comedy | 4 December 2015</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/4x0f8m273po0</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTY0MjEyMzQ1Nl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMTEwMjkxNzE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,678,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTgwOTgxNTI1M15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNzY5NDgzMzE@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Christmas Icetastrophe</title>
<summary>Storyline
A meteor enters the Earth's atmosphere and splits in two pieces. One piece strikes the center of a small mountain town and immediately starts to freeze everything and everyone nearby. The second piece forms a tropical zone amongst the snow and ice. A university grad student and a local man struggle to join the two pieces of the meteorite back together to save the town and mankind.
1h 26min | Action , Adventure , Drama | TV Movie 20 December 2014</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/iwee29efnygx</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTA4NTc4MzQzNDNeQTJeQWpwZ15BbWU4MDE2NzA4NjUx._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTA4NTc4MzQzNDNeQTJeQWpwZ15BbWU4MDE2NzA4NjUx._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Christmas Inheritance</title>
<summary>Storyline
Before ambitious heiress Ellen Langford can inherit her father's gift business, she must deliver a special Christmas card to her dad's former partner in Snow Falls, the hometown she never knew. When a snowstorm strands her at the town inn, she's forced to work for her keep, and in the process, finds romance and discovers the true gift of Christmas.
1h 44min | Romance | TV Movie 15 December 2017</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/b8wxocibp2f4</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjM2ODVjNjItMTRhNi00ZGU0LTkyM2UtNTJlMmE3NzBkMjE3XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTMxODk2OTU@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjM2ODVjNjItMTRhNi00ZGU0LTkyM2UtNTJlMmE3NzBkMjE3XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTMxODk2OTU@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Christmas Trade</title>
<summary>Storyline
Just days before Christmas, an LA real-estate lawyer and his eleven-year-old son magically swap bodies. As they walk in each other's shoes, from a cutthroat law firm and the frightening days of sixth grade, the father and son rediscover what it means to be family.LOS ANGELES, night. Inside the TAYLOR residence, ROBBY (11) sits behind a dimly lit laptop screen, scrolling through Christmas toys on a shopping website. As he climbs into bed, a loud THUMP is heard. He goes to his front door and looks around, but sees nothing. As he returns inside, a mysterious package is seen on the porch. The package is labeled, "SANTA'S MYSTERY EMPORIUM." The next morning, life in the Taylor family is complete chaos. MITCH (40s) has his cell-phone glued to his ear and pays little attention to Robby. Since Robby's mother died a few years back, it's just the two of them. It's clear that they haven't exactly established a relationship or a daily routine. Robby bugs his father about getting a Christmas tree and presents, but Mitch is too focused on his work. On their way out the door, Mitch discovers the mysterious package and thoughtlessly tosses it in the car with them. At school, Robby's life in the sixth grade consists of arithmetic, crushes, and big bully by the name of FRANCIS (11), who's mother TRISH (40s) persistently hunts the widowed Mitch like prey. At work, Mitch stresses over an injunction with the firm's biggest client Milton GREEN, who will be attending the firm's holiday party in just three days, which he is responsible for planning as well. A senior partner at the firm, HARPER SHAW, ruthlessly threatens to fire Mitch if anything goes wrong. On top of his stress, Mitch's secret girlfriend and coworker CHLOE (40s), questions their relationship and his effort to introduce her to Robby. He's one cup of decaf away from a complete mental breakdown.
1h 39min | Comedy , Family | Video 3 November 2015</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/7d3h8yyh3c0x</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTQ2MzMyODQzOF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNDM3NDkyNzE@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTQ2MzMyODQzOF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNDM3NDkyNzE@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Christmas Truce</title>
<summary>Storyline
During a 24-hour holiday truce amid the Battle of the Bulge, American army captain John Myers (Craig Olejnik) and a Belgian girl named Alina (Ali Liebert) meet and fall in love. Separated during the Battle of the Bulge, an American captain (Craig Olejnik) and the Belgian woman (Ali Liebert) he loves vow to reunite on the first Christmas Eve after the end of World War II.
1h 28min | Drama | TV Movie 17 December 2015</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/okfxq92g6pwc</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYTIzZmQ0MWYtOWQ0ZS00ZWM3LWI2NTYtZjI2NGRhZjYwNTYyXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMzQwOTg1OTQ@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYTIzZmQ0MWYtOWQ0ZS00ZWM3LWI2NTYtZjI2NGRhZjYwNTYyXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMzQwOTg1OTQ@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Christmas Under Wraps</title>
<summary>Storyline
When a doctor doesn't get the position she wanted, she ends up moving to a remote Alaskan town. She unexpectedly ends up finding love, happiness and discovers that the small town is hiding a big holiday secret.
1h 28min | Drama , Romance | TV Movie 29 November 2014</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/mft8ug3kvvep</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNjcwMjkwNTE0MF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNTQ5Mjg1MzE@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTkyMTU5NDQ2MV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMTM5Mjg1MzE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,1502,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Christmas in South Park</title>
<summary>Storyline
Howdy Ho! Mr. Hankey, everybody's favorite piece of poo, is here to show us his line up of holly jolly Christmas songs! There's S.D. Kluger singing the Mr. Hankey theme, then we've got Mr. Mackey singing Carol of the Bells, Eric Cartman singing "O Holy Night", Jesus Christ and Santa Claus singing a medley of Christmas jingles, and even Mr. Garrison wishes all the religions of the world a Merry Christmas! It really is a Merry Christmas, a Happy Hanukkah, a Krazy Kwanza, and all the rest!
1h 40min | Animation , Comedy , Musical | Video</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/gmgevgee9nxk</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYjE0NmZjMjgtZmJjOS00NTU0LWJlYzgtZjExNGUzZGVmNzRlXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTAyODkwOQ@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,666,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTg3NDcxMDY2Ml5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNTc5NDAyMg@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,1294,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Deck the Halls</title>
<summary>Storyline
Optometrist Steve Finch loves those Christmas traditions he has set up with his family and his town. As such, he has a schedule of activities for his family starting on December 1st, and is the official unofficial consultant for anything Christmas related in his town of Cloverdale, Massachusetts. During the Christmas season, the Halls move in to the house across the street from the Finch's. The Halls in general are different in outlook and temperament than the Finches. Unlike Steve, Buddy Hall scams his way through life and never follows through with anything he starts. While Kelly Finch and Tia Hall - Steve's wife and Buddy's wife respectively - and their children begin friendships based largely on those differences, Steve and Buddy butt heads based on those differences. It begins with Buddy striving to have his house seen from outer space by decorating it as lavishly and brightly as possible. One of the results of Buddy's task his that he becomes the new go to guy for anything Christmas related in Cloverdale, usurping Steve's coveted position. As Steve and Buddy's open animosity grows, they may threaten the joy of Christmas for all, most specifically their families who have their own ideas of what they would like to do over the Christmas season.
PG | 1h 33min | Comedy , Family | 1 December 2006</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/fijf76vlp0sg</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTIzNjA4OTM0OV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMDgwODkzMQ@@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTU3NjcxMDYwNV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMzE5NjQxOTE@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Die Hard</title>
<summary>Storyline
NYPD cop John McClane goes on a Christmas vacation to visit his wife Holly in Los Angeles where she works for the Nakatomi Corporation. While they are at the Nakatomi headquarters for a Christmas party, a group of robbers led by Hans Gruber take control of the building and hold everyone hostage, with the exception of John, while they plan to perform a lucrative heist. Unable to escape and with no immediate police response, John is forced to take matters into his own hands.
18 | 2h 12min | Action , Thriller | 3 February 1989</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/fk3qjqbjuzg1</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZjRlNDUxZjAtOGQ4OC00OTNlLTgxNmQtYTBmMDgwZmNmNjkxXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNzkwMjQ5NzM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,666,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZjRlNDUxZjAtOGQ4OC00OTNlLTgxNmQtYTBmMDgwZmNmNjkxXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNzkwMjQ5NzM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,666,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Donkey's Christmas Shrektacular</title>
<summary>Storyline
Donkey suggests everyone sing Christmas carols. Donkey sings "It's the Most Wonderful Time". Shrek, Fiona, the Ogre children, and the army of ogres sing an ogre version of "Jingle Bells" (i.e. "Bug Cocoon, Lick the spoon. Try our cricket slurp). Puss in Boots sings "Feliz Navidad", although he titles it "Fleas Navidad". Then everyone sings "Jingle Bell Rock", but they title it "Fairy Tale Rock".
8min | Animation , Short , Comedy | 7 December 2010</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/x80or8khvu71</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYjBhODhmMDgtODI1ZS00NDYwLWFkZWEtN2M1MWNmNzUxYTUzXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMzAzODY0NzE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,699,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTZmYTI2YjEtZjhhMi00YzljLTkwZGUtMjVlOTg5YzU3OWVhL2ltYWdlL2ltYWdlXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjA0Mzc0MzI@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Elf</title>
<summary>Storyline
Buddy was a baby in an orphanage who stowed away in Santa's sack and ended up at the North Pole. Later, as an adult human who happened to be raised by elves, Santa allows him to go to New York City to find his birth father, Walter Hobbs. Hobbs, on Santa's naughty list for being a heartless jerk, had no idea that Buddy was even born. Buddy, meanwhile, experiences the delights of New York City (and human culture) as only an elf can. When Walter's relationship with Buddy interferes with his job, he is forced to reevaluate his priorities.
PG | 1h 37min | Comedy , Family , Fantasy | 28 November 2003</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/ll5y9yw91dqo</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMzUxNzkzMzQtYjIxZC00NzU0LThkYTQtZjNhNTljMTA1MDA1L2ltYWdlL2ltYWdlXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTMxODk2OTU@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTk4MDM0MDM3N15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMzIzMzU2MzE@._V1_SY1000_SX1500_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Elf: Buddy's Musical Christmas</title>
<summary>Storyline
A musical, stop-motion adaptation of the well-known movie, Buddy, a human raised in the north pole, goes to New York to find his family.
43min | Animation , Comedy , Family | TV Movie 16 December 2014</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/iustpqxsnn24</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTQ1NTA1NzY3Nl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNTAxMDc4MzE@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjMxNjgyMDA1N15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNTY0NDE3MzE@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Elliot the Littlest Reindeer</title>
<summary>Storyline
When Blitzen announces his retirement on December 21st, a miniature horse has 3 days to fulfill his lifelong dream of earning a spot on Santa's team at the North Pole try-outs.
PG | 1h 29min | Animation, Family | 19 October 2018</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/ek9ydw62wgps</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNmMyMjkyNjEtMTAyYy00OWY3LTk3NjgtZjNjMDJjYTAxYWRkXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMzA1MjMyNTY@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,749,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNmMyMjkyNjEtMTAyYy00OWY3LTk3NjgtZjNjMDJjYTAxYWRkXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMzA1MjMyNTY@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,749,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Ernest Saves Christmas</title>
<summary>Storyline
An obnoxious and bumbling but well-meaning man attempts to help Santa Claus find a successor. Failure wouild mean that there would be no Christmas.
1h 35min | Comedy , Family , Fantasy | 17 November 1989</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/jtbqsx0d5b5z</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjI3ZGE5MTMtOTk4Ny00ZWUyLTgyMzctZjRkZDMzZWY3ZWFhXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTQxNzMzNDI@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,668,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjI3ZGE5MTMtOTk4Ny00ZWUyLTgyMzctZjRkZDMzZWY3ZWFhXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTQxNzMzNDI@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,668,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Four Christmases</title>
<summary>Storyline
Brad and Kate have been together three years, in love, having fun, doing all sorts of things together with no intention of marriage or children. Christmas morning, they're on their way to Fiji, having told their two sets of divorced parents that they're off to do charity work. Through a fluke, they have no choice but to visit each of their four idiosyncratic parents. As the day progresses, Brad and Kate remember growing up, each learns more about the other, and Kate realizes that her life may not be as good as it could be. Do they know each other well enough to weather the storms families bring?
12A | 1h 28min | Comedy , Drama , Romance | 26 November 2008</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/81rxdcx1qz55</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTQ2MjA0NDAwNF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwOTU4MTM5MQ@@._V1_SY1000_SX675_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTQ2MjA0NDAwNF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwOTU4MTM5MQ@@._V1_SY1000_SX675_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Fred Claus</title>
<summary>Storyline
During childhood, Fred Claus suffered his younger brother Nick's saintliness. Jump ahead: Fred is a fast-talking, genial but self-centered guy in Chicago looking for $50,000 to open an off-track-betting shop. When one scam goes awry, he calls Nick at the North Pole for a loan: Nick will give him the money only if Fred comes up to help a few days with the Christmas rush. After his girlfriend dumps him, Fred heads north. Santa's facing an audit from an efficiency expert, and it's not pleasant. Fred's job is to review charts and determine who's naughty and who's nice. Is there any fraternal feeling left, can either learn from the other, and what about Santa getting fired?
PG | 1h 56min | Comedy , Family , Fantasy | 30 November 2007</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/w586z5lad3gl</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTY0NDEwNzc0N15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNjgxNzUzMw@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,676,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTgyNjQ2NjMyNV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMDIwNzUzMw@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,1504,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Frozen</title>
<summary>Storyline
Fearless optimist Anna teams up with rugged mountain man Kristoff and his loyal reindeer Sven and sets off on an epic journey to find her sister Elsa, whose icy powers have trapped the kingdom of Arendelle in eternal winter. Encountering Everest-like conditions, mystical trolls and a hilarious snowman named Olaf, Anna and Kristoff battle the elements in a race to save the kingdom. From the outside Elsa looks poised, regal and reserved, but in reality she lives in fear as she wrestles with a mighty secret: she was born with the power to create ice and snow. It's a beautiful ability, but also extremely dangerous. Haunted by the moment her magic nearly killed her younger sister Anna, Elsa has isolated herself, spending every waking minute trying to suppress her growing powers. Her mounting emotions trigger the magic, accidentally setting off an eternal winter that she can't stop. She fears she's becoming a monster and that no one, not even her sister, can help her.
PG | 1h 42min | Animation , Adventure , Comedy | 6 December 2013</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/e21kdpr8ns54</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTQ1MjQwMTE5OF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNjk3MTcyMDE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTQ1MjQwMTE5OF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNjk3MTcyMDE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Get Santa</title>
<summary>Storyline
A father and son who team up to save Christmas once they discover Santa Claus sleeping in their garage after crashing his sleigh and finding himself on the run from the police.
U | 1h 42min | Comedy , Family | 5 December 2014</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/uhlqqqidxodw</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNTU0OTk3MDg1Ml5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNjk0MjkxMzE@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjI1MDQ2MDI0N15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNTc3NDEwMzE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,1333,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Gremlins</title>
<summary>Storyline
Minature green monsters tear through the small town of Kingston Falls. Hijinks ensue as a mild-mannered bank teller releases these hideous loonies after gaining a new pet and violating two of three simple rules: No water (violated), no food after midnight (violated), and no bright light. Hilarious mayhem and destruction in a town straight out of Norman Rockwell. So, when your washing machine blows up or your TV goes on the fritz, before you call the repair man, turn on all the lights and look under all the beds. 'Cause you never can tell, there just might be a gremlin in your house.
15 | 1h 46min | Comedy , Fantasy , Horror | 7 December 1984</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/d0jiizpstddy</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZDVjN2FkYTQtNTBlOC00MjM5LTgzMWEtZWRlNGUyYmNiOTFiXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTQxNzMzNDI@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZDVjN2FkYTQtNTBlOC00MjM5LTgzMWEtZWRlNGUyYmNiOTFiXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTQxNzMzNDI@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Grumpy Cat's Worst Christmas Ever</title>
<summary>Storyline
Grumpy Cat is a lonely cat living in a mall pet shop. Because she never gets chosen by customers, she develops a sour outlook on life...until one day during the holidays, a very special 12-year-old girl named Chyrstal enters the pet store and falls in love with her after realizing she is the only person who can hear this unique cat talk. As the two develop a close friendship during the holiday rush, Grumpy reluctantly thwarts the kidnapping of an exotic dog she dislikes, and on Christmas Eve rescues Chyrstal after the mall closes. Through her adventures, will Grumpy learn the true meaning of Christmas? Or will it be, in her words, the "Worst. Christmas. Ever?"
PG | 1h 27min | Adventure , Comedy | TV Movie 4 December 2014</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/u1um54z4o9ae</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMzIwNDMyNzkzNV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNzE1OTI2MzE@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjE1MzUwOTE0MF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNjQzODgxMzE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,1502,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Home Alone</title>
<summary>Storyline
It is Christmas time and the McCallister family is preparing for a vacation in Paris, France. But the youngest in the family named Kevin got into a scuffle with his older brother Buzz and was sent to his room which is on the third floor of his house. Then, the next morning, while the rest of the family was in a rush to make it to the airport on time, they completely forgot about Kevin who now has the house all to himself. Being home alone was fun for Kevin, having a pizza all to himself, jumping on his parents' bed, and making a mess. Then, Kevin discovers about two burglars, Harry and Marv, about to rob his house on Christmas Eve. Kevin acts quickly by wiring his own house with makeshift booby traps to stop the burglars and to bring them to justice.
PG | 1h 43min | Comedy , Family | 7 December 1990</summary>
<link>https://uptostream.com/tvtossg1ziyb</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMzFkM2YwOTQtYzk2Mi00N2VlLWE3NTItN2YwNDg1YmY0ZDNmXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTMxODk2OTU@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,672,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZTBiNmQ2ZGItYzUzNy00MmRmLWEwMDctZWFlM2QzNWUyY2RhXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMzEzMjg5NjA@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,972_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Home Alone 2: Lost in New York</title>
<summary>Storyline
Kevin McCallister is back. But this time he's in New York City with enough cash and credit cards to turn the Big Apple into his very own playground. But Kevin won't be alone for long. The notorious Wet Bandits, Harry and Marv, still smarting from their last encounter with Kevin, are bound for New York too, plotting a huge holiday heist! Kevin's ready to welcome them with more battery of booby traps the bumbling bandits will never forget!
PG | 2h | Adventure , Comedy , Family | 11 December 1992</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/5bik42j82ih2</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNDI1MzM0Y2YtYmIyMS00ODE3LTlhZjEtZTUyNmEzMTNhZWU5XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTQxNzMzNDI@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZGJiY2I2MTgtM2QxZi00NWM0LThiZmUtY2ZlYjRkZThjNTJmXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNzQ1NjgzOTA@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,962_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Home Alone 3</title>
<summary>Storyline
Four high-tech industrial spies, Beaupre, Alice, Jernigan and Unger, steal a top-secret microchip, and, to fool customs, hide it in a remote-control toy car. Through a baggage mix-up at the airport, grumpy old Mrs.Hess gets the toy and gives it to her neighbor, 8-year-old Alex. Spies want to get the toy back before their clients get angry and decide to burglarize every house at Alex's street to find the chip. But Alex is prepared for their visit.
PG | 1h 42min | Comedy , Crime , Family | 19 December 1997</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/57di66qfw4uo</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZTJhYjVhOWMtYTUyOS00NWM0LThjNzYtZWYxOTkwN2FhODg2XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTQxNzMzNDI@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,669,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTcwMTMxMTcwNV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTYwOTc5MDA3._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Home Alone 4</title>
<summary>Storyline
Kevin McCallister's parents have split up. Now living with his mom, he decides to spend Christmas with his dad at the mansion of his father's rich girlfriend, Natalie. Meanwhile robber Marv Merchants, one of the villains from the first two movies, partners up with a new criminal named Vera to hit Natalie's mansion.
U | 1h 29min | Comedy , Crime , Family | TV Movie 3 November 2002</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/3xyt5xrkvdb9</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTAzNjM3OTEwNjNeQTJeQWpwZ15BbWU3MDk1ODIwMDE@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BOWZmMjA3NWMtNTM1OS00OWM5LThkNTUtYzM0NjE4NGMyZTZjL2ltYWdlL2ltYWdlXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjc4NDc1OTM@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Home Alone 5: The Holiday Heist</title>
<summary>Storyline
Finn Baxter and his family move from California to Maine to their new house. Finn is terrified, and believes the house is haunted. While he sets up traps to catch the "ghost", his parents get stranded across town, and Finn is home alone with his sister. Their house is targeted by three thieves.
PG | 1h 27min | Comedy , Crime , Family | TV Movie 25 November 2012</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/5zob1wfltmhl</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMzg2MDYyODMtMDhkYS00MWIyLWI2ZjItYmUwNmFjYjRhMWM3XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNDgyODgxNjE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,666,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZjA3ODQ0NTUtMTg4OS00OGY2LWE1NjUtMTE5NmUwYTkwMjZiXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNDgyODgxNjE@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>How the Grinch Stole Christmas</title>
<summary>Storyline
Inside a snowflake exists the magical land of Whoville. In Whoville, live the Whos, an almost mutated sort of munchkinlike people. All the Whos love Christmas, yet just outside of their beloved Whoville lives the Grinch. The Grinch is a nasty creature that hates Christmas, and plots to steal it away from the Whos which he equally abhors. Yet a small child, Cindy Lou Who, decides to try befriend the Grinch.
PG | 1h 44min | Comedy , Family , Fantasy | 1 December 2000</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/7jy371rrun2l</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNWNiNTczNzEtMjQyZC00MjFmLTkzMDMtODk4ZGMyZmE0N2E4XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTMxODk2OTU@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNWJkM2FlOGItOGFmYS00MjI4LWFjNmUtMzkxNGUzZGZmMGYyXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNDQxNjcxNQ@@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>I Am Santa Claus</title>
<summary>Storyline
We have documented an entire year in the lives of five real-bearded professional Santa Clauses to find out what the rest of the year is like for a man who perpetually looks like Jolly Saint Nick. In the process, they are shown for who they actually are, flawed, flesh and blood men who feel an overbearing responsibility to protect the integrity of the spotless, untarnished reputation of the 'Red Suit.' 'I Am Santa Claus' is a documentary that poses a question about a ubiquitous holiday figure that few parents ever ask themselves; 'Whose lap is my child sitting on?'
1h 29min | Documentary , Comedy , Drama | 4 November 2014</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/02p5bvfr2v4d</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTQ3NTYyNTk0OV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMjk5Mzc4MDE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,666,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTQ3NTYyNTk0OV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMjk5Mzc4MDE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,666,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Ice Age: A Mammoth Christmas</title>
<summary>Storyline
When Sid accidentally destroys Manny's heirloom Christmas rock and ends up on Santa's naughty list, he leads a hilarious quest to the North Pole to make things right and ends up making things much worse. Now it's up to Manny and his prehistoric posse to band together and save Christmas for the entire world.
U | 26min | Animation , Short , Adventure | TV Short 24 November 2011</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/ongfsy7o0bdp</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYTMzMjZhNjAtZDBmMS00MzA0LTljNjUtZGNlMGNiYTc5ODg4XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTE0MDY4Mjk@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,713,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNTc1ZjQ2MDktMTZlMy00ZTlhLThjYTMtYzZkYjE0ZjUwM2E5XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNDgyODgxNjE@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>It's a SpongeBob Christmas!</title>
<summary>Storyline
Plankton, Mr. Krabs' nemesis, vows to get his Christmas wish - obtaining the Krusty Krab's secret Krabby Patty formula - by turning everyone bad in Bikini Bottom with the help of his special jerktonium-laced fruitcake.
U | 23min | Animation , Comedy , Family | Episode aired 23 November 2012</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/1frrynwlnxuy</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjAwOTQzNjQ5NV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMzQ0OTAxMzE@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjIzMTE2Nzg2MV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNTM3NDg5MTE@._V1_SY1000_SX1500_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Jack Frost</title>
<summary>Storyline
Jack Frost is a singer who's on the road most of the time so he can't spend a lot of time with his son Charlie, although they love each other very much. When Jack dies in a car accident, Charlie becomes a very sad young man, until... Jack returns as a snowman! Now they can do all the things they've missed when Jack was human, but what will people think when they see Charlie talking to a snowman and what will happen when the weather gets warmer?
PG | 1h 41min | Comedy , Drama , Family | 12 February 1999</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/ym73w4t44kqo</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BOTE4YWIzNjItZWNhNi00Y2E1LTgyODktMTUzM2ZkMmJlNDFlL2ltYWdlXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjg4NzYzMzA@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTUzNDUzNjUxMF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwODEyMTk0MDI@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Jingle All the Way</title>
<summary>Storyline
Meet Howard Langston, a salesman for a mattress company is constantly busy at his job, and he also constantly disappoints his son, after he misses his son's karate exposition, he tries hard to come up with a way to make it up to him, this is when his son tells Howard that he wants for Christmas is an action figure of his son's television hero, Turbo Man. Unfortunately for Howard, it is Christmas Eve, and every store is sold out of Turbo Man figures, now Howard must travel all over town and compete with everybody else including a mail man named Myron to find a Turbo Man action figure, and to make it to the Wintertainment parade which will feature Turbo Man.
PG | 1h 29min | Comedy , Family | 6 December 1996</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/7eej8jmo3nbk</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMmJlYzViNzctMjQ1Ni00ZWQ4LThkN2YtMzI2ZGU5Nzk0NTAyXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTQxNzMzNDI@._V1_SY999_CR0,0,656,999_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMmJlYzViNzctMjQ1Ni00ZWQ4LThkN2YtMzI2ZGU5Nzk0NTAyXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTQxNzMzNDI@._V1_SY999_CR0,0,656,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Jingle All the Way 2</title>
<summary>Storyline
Two desperate dads compete in a no-holds-barred battle to be the best father and make this the best Christmas ever. Fun-loving, laid-back dad Larry is having a bear of a time finding the perfect Christmas gift for his eight-year-old daughter, Noel. The season's hottest toy, The Harrison Bear, is all sold out, and Noel's new stepfather wants to keep it that way - so he can be the one to make her holiday wish come true. When Larry learns all Noel wants for Christmas is the bear, he'll stop at nothing to make his little girl happy and get her the toy of her dreams.
U | 1h 33min | Comedy , Family | Video 29 October 2014</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/mygbazrzq00k</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYzMzOTU0ZGUtOGIxYi00MDU2LWIyZmItMTZkOGM3MzQxNjU5XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTM3MDMyMDQ@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjIxNjI1NzU5NV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwOTExNzYxMzE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,1501,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Just in Time for Christmas</title>
<summary>Storyline
A young psychology professor must choose between moving across the country for her dream job or staying in her hometown to marry the man of her dreams. On a foggy December night, she gets little help from a Coachman, who brings her three years into the future and shows her what her life will become.
U | 1h 36min | Comedy , Romance | TV Movie 5 December 2015</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/5cta4p13kt4v</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNmMxYjBjMTctOWYwZS00YjVhLWE3MjEtNmFhYzQyY2YwYzIxXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNzk0NTA5NQ@@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNmMxYjBjMTctOWYwZS00YjVhLWE3MjEtNmFhYzQyY2YwYzIxXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNzk0NTA5NQ@@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Love Actually</title>
<summary>Storyline
Set almost entirely in London, England during five frantic weeks before Christmas follows a web-like pattern of inter-related, loosely related and unrelated stories of a dozen or more various individuals with their love lives, or lack of them. The central character is the new bachelor prime minister David who cannot express his growing feelings for his new personal assistant Natalie. The prime minister's older sister Karen slowly grows aware of her husband Harry's flirtation with an office worker named Mia. Karen's friend Daniel is a recently widowed writer whose 11-year-old son asks for love advice about a girl he has a crush on. Meanwhile, Jamie is another writer who leaves his girlfriend after catching her cheating on him and travels to France to write a novel where he pursues a possible romance with his non-English speaking Portuguese maid Aurelia. Also, Harry's American secretary Sarah questions a romance she pursues with the office hunk Karl, but her personal family problems get in the way. Other secondary characters involve a photographer who pursues his best friend's new wife Juliet; a pair of movie stand-ins, named John and Judy, who grow closer after their simulated love scenes; a libidinous chum who wants to travel to Wisconsin, USA to score with women; and a burned-out former rock star named Billy Mack who is the main connection between all stories involved.
15 | 2h 15min | Comedy , Drama , Romance | 21 November 2003</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/bmxel3guokkp</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTY4NjQ5NDc0Nl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTYwNjk5NDM3._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTk4NDgxOTA0OV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNDQxMTQzNDM@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Madagascar Penguins in a Christmas Caper</title>
<summary>Storyline
On Christmas Eve, Private slips out of the zoo for some last-minute shopping. In the city he's mistaken as a cute chew toy by a mean old woman named Nana, who gives Private to her vicious dog, Mr. Chew. On a mission to rescue their penguin pal, Skipper, Kowalski and Rico risk life and flipper as they take on Nana and Mr. Chew with an explosive solution that will leave you laughing out loud.
U | 11min | Animation , Short , Comedy | 8 October 2005</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/pqcq1f0esg0y</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNDE4MmY1NjMtZmVmNC00MjFhLWJjYzktNWNlY2QzZWZiNTIzL2ltYWdlL2ltYWdlXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjg5MzE4NTA@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,701,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNjVmMDBhMTEtYjUxMi00NGY3LWE0MDUtMDRkOTBhODEzZmM2XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNDgyODgxNjE@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Merry Madagascar</title>
<summary>Storyline
When Santa and his reindeer crash onto Madagascar it's up to Alex, Marty, Gloria, Melvin, and the penguins to save Christmas.
U | 28min | Animation , Short , Adventure | TV Short 17 November 2009</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/lni7v2ox4h6e</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNWZlMjRkYjItOGRlOS00MmJkLWI0OWUtZjIyYTUxZTY0NGVmXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNDgyODgxNjE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,666,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjE0NDIyOTcyMl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMjUzODAwMw@@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Mickey's Magical Christmas: Snowed in at the House of Mouse</title>
<summary>Storyline
After everyone is snowed in at the House of Mouse, Mickey suggests they throw their own Christmas party. Everyone is happy, except for Donald who just isn't in to the Christmas spirit. So Mickey shows a series of cartoons that show just what Christmas is all about. It features a star studded cast of Disney characters from everyone's favorite animated Disney movies.
U | 1h 5min | Animation, Adventure, Comedy | Video 6 November 2001</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/8tfaycyc54jk</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTkyODU0MTA1MF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNzEzODcxMQ@@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTkyODU0MTA1MF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNzEzODcxMQ@@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Mickey's Once Upon a Christmas</title>
<summary>Storyline
A Christmas themed, three-part anthology-style video. The first part, "Donald Duck: Stuck on Christmas", is essentially a retelling of Groundhog Day (1993), with Huey, Dewey, and Louie reliving Christmas ad infinitum. Next is "A Very Goofy Christmas", in which Goofy tries to overcome his son's skepticism about Santa Claus. Finally, "Mickey & Minnie's Gift Of The Magi" recreate the classic tale of ironic Christmas selflessness. The stories are linked together by narration by Kelsey Grammer.
U | 1h 6min | Animation , Comedy , Family | Video 11 December 2000</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/jqu3qkurb422</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTI3OTI2NTI0N15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNzQzMzYyMQ@@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTI3OTI2NTI0N15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNzQzMzYyMQ@@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Mickey's Twice Upon a Christmas</title>
<summary>Storyline
Mickey and all his Disney pals star in an original movie about the importance of opening your heart to the true spirit of Christmas. Stubborn old Donald tries in vain to resist the joys of the season, and Mickey and Pluto learn a great lesson about the power of friendship.
U | 1h 8min | Animation , Comedy , Family | Video 15 November 2004</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/qdn6v0xiy5xz</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjI4ODk0MDg2NV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMTM2MzcyMQ@@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYjM0MjZlMjQtMDk1ZC00Nzk2LThiODctOGQyNjA3MTA5NmFmXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTc0NjY1ODk@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Miracle on 34th Street (1947)</title>
<summary>Storyline
At the Macy's Department Store Thanksgiving Day parade, the actor playing Santa is discovered to be drunk by a whiskered old man. Doris Walker, the no nonsense special events director, persuades the old man to take his place. The old man proves to be a sensation and is quickly recruited to be the store Santa at the main Macy's outlet. While he is successful, Ms. Walker learns that he calls himself Kris Kringle and he claims to be the actual Santa Claus. Despite reassurances by Kringle's doctor that he is harmless, Doris still has misgivings, especially when she has cynically trained herself, and especially her daughter, Susan, to reject all notions of belief and fantasy. And yet, people, especially Susan, begin to notice there is something special about Kris and his determination to advance the true spirit of Christmas amidst the rampant commercialism around him and succeeding in improbable ways. When a raucous conflict with the store's cruelly incompetent psychologist erupts, Kris finds himself held at Bellevue where, in despair, he deliberately fails a mental examination to ensure his commitment. All seems lost until Doris' friend, Fred Gaily, reassures Kris of his worth and agrees to represent him in the fight to secure his release. To achieve that, Fred arranges a formal hearing in which he argues that Kris is sane because he is in fact Santa Claus. What ensues is a bizarre hearing in which people's beliefs are reexamined and put to the test, but even so, it's going to take a miracle for Kris to win.
U | 1h 36min | Comedy , Drama , Family | 2 October 1947</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/a4w1dudqxa0k</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTYwMzUwNjkyM15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwODE3OTgwMzE@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTYwMzUwNjkyM15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwODE3OTgwMzE@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Miracle on 34th Street (1994)</title>
<summary>Storyline
A little girl discovers dreams do come true if you really believe. Six-year-old Susan has doubts about childhood's most enduring miracle - Santa Claus. Her mother told her the "secret" about Santa a long time ago, so Susan doesn't expect to receive the most important gifts on her Christmas list. But after meeting a special department store Santa who's convinced he's the real thing, Susan is given the most precious gift of all - something to believe in.
U | 1h 54min | Family , Fantasy | 18 November 1994</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/r93olp7ppb1d</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTg5MTQxNDMxNl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTYwNzE4Mzg4._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNzQwMzIxNTk2N15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMjk0MDg4MDI@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,888_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Moomins and the Winter Wonderland</title>
<summary>Storyline
Moomintroll decides to stay awake to explore the winter instead of having his winter slumber as usually. Winter is certainly totally different than he had imagined.
1h 22min | Animation , Adventure , Comedy | 1 December 2017</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/kru2mbitn95q</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZjY1MzAyMjUtZTJjYi00OGFjLWFjZTItOTdkODZkODZmMDMwXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTYzMjkwNjU@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,666,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMzQwNjY2MTctMDk3OS00YmQyLWE3YzAtNzU1NDgyZTFlYTI5XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMDgxMjcwNw@@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>My Christmas Dream</title>
<summary>Storyline
A department store, McDougal's, is expanding and opening a store in Paris. The manager, Christina Masters, wants the job and tries to create the best holiday display. She turns to Kurt Stone for help and as they work together, she starts falling in love with him. Now she has to choose between the dream job in Paris or staying put with Kurt.
2h | Comedy, Romance | TV Movie 19 November 2016</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/4f5apsnotw3n</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYjQxMWExYjAtOThmNC00MTE2LTg4OTMtZGNiNTdkMWYyNGJlXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjg5MzE4NTA@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYjQxMWExYjAtOThmNC00MTE2LTg4OTMtZGNiNTdkMWYyNGJlXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjg5MzE4NTA@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>National Lampoon's Christmas Vacation</title>
<summary>Storyline
It's Christmas time and the Griswolds are preparing for a family seasonal celebration, but things never run smoothly for Clark, his wife Ellen and their two kids. Clark's continual bad luck is worsened by his obnoxious family guests, but he manages to keep going knowing that his Christmas bonus is due soon.
PG | 1h 37min | Comedy | 1 December 1989</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/t9ssvgcrzsoy</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMGZkMWQ2MzMtYTkxYS00OThmLWI0ZTQtNmY0ZTkyY2E4MjliXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTQxNzMzNDI@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMzVkZjFjNDMtMzE5ZS00ZDY5LWJjNTMtMmVhMDk2NzYwYzhjXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNzc5NjM0NA@@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Nativity!</title>
<summary>Storyline
This Christmas, primary school teacher Paul Maddens is charged with producing the school's nativity play. Competing against the posh rival school for the honor of best reviewed show in town, the stakes are raised when Paul idly boasts that his ex-girlfriend Jennifer, a Hollywood Producer, is coming to see his show with a view to turning it into a film. The only trouble is - they haven't spoken in years. With eccentric assistant Mr Poppy fuelling his 'little white lie', Maddens suddenly finds himself a local celebrity and at the center of quarreling parents and over-excited children desperate in their bid for fame and fortune. Maddens' only hope is to get back in touch with Jennifer and lure Hollywood to town so that everybody's Christmas wishes come true.
U | 1h 45min | Comedy , Family | 27 November 2009</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/kt1hnjlgpuzv</link>
<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w600_and_h900_bestv2/hIzGgnRUriIXHGtH6I0xxTT3cjw.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTUwMjMwMzE1NF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMDY2MTYwMw@@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Nativity 2: Danger in the Manger!</title>
<summary>Storyline
This sequel to the popular British comedy sees a new teacher (David Tennant) take over. When he enters his school in the National 'Song for Christmas' Competition, he and his pregnant wife, and the schoolchildren, embark on an epic road trip that ends up with a birth and a donkey, where he must embrace his fears and become a hero.
U | 1h 45min | Comedy | 23 November 2012</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/gep9ds6ltgil</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTYzMDM0MzM0Ml5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNjIxMTkyMTE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,686,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/dQaR8iVdvqT9ROxW3gr7YdmNTrI.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Nativity 3: Dude, Where's My Donkey?!</title>
<summary>Storyline
The pupils of St Bernadette's and the madcap Mr Poppy (MARC WOOTTON) are back! When their new teacher Mr Shepherd (MARTIN CLUNES) loses his memory as well as Archie the Donkey, it's up to them to save the day and reunite him with his fiancée Sophie (CATHERINE TATE) in New York. Prepare for a race against time, fantastic flashmobs and plenty of Christmas fun on their greatest adventure yet.
U | 1h 49min | Comedy | 14 November 2014</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/gberoovra9aj</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTUxOTQ1NTgyOF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMzAxMzU4MjE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BODkwMDQ4MzU1NV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMjM2NjQ0MzE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,1503,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>New Year's Eve</title>
<summary>Storyline
Set during New Year's Eve in New York city, this movie follows several people and how the day affects them. Kim is a single mother who still thinks of her daughter, Hailey as a child who wants to go out with a boy so that she could kiss him at midnight. Claire, who is in charge of the city's annual tradition, the ball drop on Times Square. And when something goes wrong she has to ask an electrician, who was fired, to come and fix it. Laura, a chef who is cooking the New year's Eve party for a record company who runs into Jensen, her ex who's a singer and performing at the party. While he tries to apologize for how things ended, she refuses to accept it. Ingrid, a woman who works at the record company, after having a near death experience, decides to quit her job and asks a young messenger, Paul to help her fulfill her resolutions. And at a hospital, Stan, a man who is in the final stages of cancer, only wishes to see the ball drop. Also Griffin and Tess, a couple who are expecting, want to be the ones who give birth first after New Year because of the available cash prize; but another couple is also about to give birth. Randy a man who's not exactly fond of the holiday because of something that happened, finds himself trapped in an elevator with a singer who is one of Jensen's back up singers when he performs at Times Square. And Sam, son of the owner of the record company, who is out of town and is trying to get back to the city so that he could give a speech at the party, but when he has an accident and since it's a holiday, his car can't be fixed so he hitches a ride with some people going to the city. But it seems he has another reason why he needs to get back.
12A | 1h 53min | Comedy , Romance | 8 December 2011</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/3iyvbo042p9p</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjI2Mzg2MDQxOV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNzc3NTY5Ng@@._V1_SY1000_SX625_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZWEwYzI1Y2QtYjFmNC00NTVmLWE5ZDAtYzM3NzQ3MzNkZjdmXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjI2NzE2MDg@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Northpole: Open for Christmas</title>
<summary>Storyline
A successful businesswoman, Mackenzie, inherits her beloved aunt's inn, and chooses to restore the hotel to its original grandeur only to sell it right before Christmas. Unbeknownst to Mackenzie, she receives some unexpected help from a team of elves headed by the cheerful Clementine, who helps Mackenzie rediscover the true meaning of Christmas.
U | 1h 23min | Fantasy | TV Movie 21 November 2015</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/nrljxixwiq6h</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYWE2Y2Y2NDEtZjBkZS00NWZlLWI4ZWUtYWJhNmE4ODFjNzJmXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjg5MzE4NTA@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYWE2Y2Y2NDEtZjBkZS00NWZlLWI4ZWUtYWJhNmE4ODFjNzJmXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjg5MzE4NTA@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Office Christmas Party</title>
<summary>Storyline
When the CEO (Jennifer Aniston) tries to close her hard-partying brother's branch, he (T.J. Miller) and his Chief Technical Officer (Jason Bateman) must rally their co-workers and host an epic office Christmas party in an effort to impress a potential client and close a sale that will save their jobs.
15 | 1h 45min | Comedy | 7 December 2016</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/2qneszhjp1rk</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNTI2MDE5MjQ3MV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNjA0MTUzMDI@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTg2NjUxODg4Ml5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMjE3MzA1MDI@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,675,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Olaf's Frozen Adventure</title>
<summary>Storyline
Olaf teams up with Sven on a merry mission in Walt Disney Animation Studios' 21-minute featurette "Olaf's Frozen Adventure." It's the first holiday season since the gates reopened and Anna and Elsa host a celebration for all of Arendelle. When the townspeople unexpectedly leave early to enjoy their individual holiday customs, the sisters realize they have no family traditions of their own. So, Olaf sets out to comb the kingdom to bring home the best traditions and save this first Christmas for his friends.
U | 22min | Animation , Short , Adventure | 19 January 2018</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/efqnvdp44yy8</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZmU4MDRhNGQtODAyMC00ZmU0LWFmMWEtZTYxYzhhOTczYjhjXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNDI2NzczOTg@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZmU4MDRhNGQtODAyMC00ZmU0LWFmMWEtZTYxYzhhOTczYjhjXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNDI2NzczOTg@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Peppa Pig: Peppa's Christmas</title>
<summary>Storyline
Peppa and family are getting ready for Christmas. Peppa and George post letters to Santa, then head to Miss Rabbit's tree shop to buy a Christmas Tree.
1h | Animation | Video</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/w6sy778r2ohz</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTA3ODUwMTA1OTBeQTJeQWpwZ15BbWU4MDQ3MDM2MDgx._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTA3ODUwMTA1OTBeQTJeQWpwZ15BbWU4MDQ3MDM2MDgx._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Rudolph the Red-Nosed Reindeer (1964)</title>
<summary>Storyline
Sam the snowman tells us the story of a young red-nosed reindeer who, after being ousted from the reindeer games because of his beaming honker, teams up with Hermey, an elf who wants to be a dentist, and Yukon Cornelius, the prospector. They run into the Abominable Snowman and find a whole island of misfit toys. Rudolph vows to see if he can get Santa to help the toys, and he goes back to the North Pole on Christmas Eve. But Santa's sleigh is fogged in. But when Santa looks over Rudolph, he gets a very bright idea.
U | 47min | Animation , Adventure , Comedy | TV Movie 6 December 1964</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/o9vtnmm0h8vs</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYjdjZjkyYjUtOWJiZC00ZTE2LTk4MDktZjliOTk5ZDk5ZTZhXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTAyODkwOQ@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,701,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYjQ1NmY4NzgtODBlZS00NDAxLTg1M2MtZDUzMDQ1ZTQxODEyXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNDU4MDA0NTM@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Rudolph the Red-Nosed Reindeer (1998)</title>
<summary>Storyline
When Rudolph is born with a red nose he is bullied through out his younger years, but when Stormella closes her bridge of to the public and threaten to put Santa out of business for good this starts a chain of events that brings Rudolph from zero to hero don't miss it
U | 1h 23min | Animation , Adventure , Family | 16 October 1998</summary>
<link>http://s1.tinydl.info/Movies2/Rudolph%20the%20Red-Nosed%20Reindeer%201998/Rudolph_the_RedNosed_Reindeer_1998_DVDRip_AC3_BHRG_TINYMZ.avi</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTUxMDU3NTU5NV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTYwNTc5MjM5._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYzc4OTAyYjQtZDY2Yy00M2JmLWJlZGItMzNiMWQ3YzkzZDYzXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTc0NjY1ODk@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Santa Buddies</title>
<summary>Storyline
At the North Pole, Santa Claus (Father Christmas) and his chief dog Santa Paws worry as the whole toy processing system is threatened by the weakening of its magical power source, the icicle drawing on Christmas spirit. When harshly rebuked Puppy Paws, wishing there was no Christmas, and he a regular dog, runs away to Fernfield and joins the five Buddies siblings, power falls beneath minimum. Chief Elf Eli finds his trace, and travels in an attempt to save his and the world's Christmas spirit, but the six puppies face misunderstandings, and the grim dog catcher Stan Cruge.
U | 1h 28min | Adventure , Family , Fantasy | Video 22 October 2009</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/mctei8tv608s</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTgyMTIyMjI5OF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNTIzOTIxMw@@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTgyMTIyMjI5OF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNTIzOTIxMw@@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Santa Claus The Movie</title>
<summary>Storyline
This is the story of a master toymaker who discovers a magical kingdom of elves in the North Pole and becomes Santa Claus. But when Santa's eager-to-please elf Patch leaves the North Pole for the big streets of New York City, he becomes mixed up with a dastardly toy tycoon's plans to take over Christmas. And so begins Santa's adventure - to rescue his faithful elf and to save Christmas for all the children of the world!
U | 1h 47min | Adventure , Family , Fantasy | 29 November 1985</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/zkftmnbbzbwe</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTc1ODEyMTc5Ml5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwODkzMTIzMQ@@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTU3NDU1ODk1NF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNDAyODU4MDI@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Santa Claws</title>
<summary>Storyline
Tommy, who is unable to celebrate Christmas because his mom says Santa isn't real, leaves his kittens out for Santa to take back to the North Pole, but after a major allergic reaction Santa can't fly the sleigh or deliver presents anymore, so the kittens have to deliver the rest of the presents to all the boys and girls before sunrise.
U | 1h 26min | Family , Fantasy | 3 December 2015</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/9ejlf3cdmvso</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTY1MTM2MTcxMl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwODE0NTM0MjE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,713,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTY1MTM2MTcxMl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwODE0NTM0MjE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,713,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Santa's Little Helper</title>
<summary>Storyline
After getting fired from his job, a slick, fast-talking businessman (The Miz) is thrown into an elf competition to become Santa¹s next second-in-command. Put through a series of rigorous training exercises to prepare for the contest, The Miz and another aspiring elf go head-to-head in the hopes of becoming Santa¹s Little Helper.
12 | 1h 31min | Family | Video 23 November 2015</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/nnmmcksgjqco</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNGEyYzE2ZGUtMGVlMi00ZDdhLWEyYjctYmJlNDczYjhjZWVjL2ltYWdlXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjczMzc5NzQ@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZjFkMGU3ZTEtZjAyMi00OWE2LTlmNmUtMTcwMzhlYTkzMWY2L2ltYWdlXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjczMzc5NzQ@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Saving Santa</title>
<summary>Storyline
With dreams of being an inventor, opportunist and eccentric elf Bernard D. Elf is made to feel a fool yet again when his innovative creation to bring back people's favourite Christmas memories back to life fails miserably. However he is then presented with the perfect opportunity to prove his worth, when Santa is kidnapped by the evil Neville Baddington, and his demanding mother Vera, who have their heart set on discovering Santa's big secret: how he delivers presents across the world in just one night. However Bernard knows how he does it, using a time travelling device to ensure all children wake up on Christmas morning with their presents under the tree. The elf decides to use this to his advantage, as he plans on going back in time and preventing the abduction from ever happening, and save Santa - and Christmas - for the entire world.
U | 1h 23min | Animation , Adventure , Comedy | Video 5 November 2013</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/6wksbd1jw3s9</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNmJiNmVhMTctNTExYi00NDc5LTgyNWEtMTcyYzE5MDM2YmEwXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTkzODUwNzk@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,706,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNmJiNmVhMTctNTExYi00NDc5LTgyNWEtMTcyYzE5MDM2YmEwXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTkzODUwNzk@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,706,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Scoot & Kassie's Christmas Adventure</title>
<summary>Storyline
It's the Christmas season. Widowed Paul Stevenson and his two daughters, fifteen year old Esther Stevenson and ten year old Kassie Stevenson, have just moved to the winter resort town of Heber Valley, Utah, where Paul will be the general manager of the Heber Valley Bank. Kassie in particular is afraid she won't make friends, especially since her school doesn't have a music program. Music and singing is one of her passions, one of the ways she stays connected to the memory of her musician mother. Kassie stumbles upon an injured and abandoned German Shepard, who, with Esther's help, nurses him back to health while hiding the fact of who they eventually name Scoot from their father, who they believe will not let them keep him. But upon finding out about him, Paul does allow them to keep Scoot, who Kassie considers her first real friend in Heber Valley. Kassie is eventually able to use music in the form of the children's choir at the local church to find her place in town. She and the other choir kids mobilize their talents to raise money for the Toys for Tots Christmas charity, donations which were in short supply due largely to the fact of there being no snow in a town that relies on winter tourists. As the donations, which are being kept in a locked glass box in the middle of bank, increase, Kassie and her friends are unaware of two things. First, the two security guards Paul just hired are really criminals who plan to rob the Toys for Tots donation box. And second, Scoot is really a Fort Collins, Colorado police dog named Jake who thwarted the two crooks' last robbery, who was left for dead by the two crooks when they had the opportunity for revenge, and who remembers well the two who tried to kill him.
1h 26min | Family | 5 November 2013</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/kt1hnjlgpuzv</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjE3NjY1NzMwNF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwOTc0NzA2MDE@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjE3NjY1NzMwNF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwOTc0NzA2MDE@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Scrooge (1970)</title>
<summary>Storyline
In 1860, cranky old miser Ebenezer Scrooge hates Christmas; loathes people and defends the decrease of the surplus of poor population; runs his bank exploiting his employee Bob Cratchit and clients, giving a bitter treatment to his own nephew and acquaintances. However, on Christmas Eve, he is visited by the doomed ghost of his former partner Jacob Marley that tells him that three spirits would visit him that night. The first one, the spirit of Christmas Past, recalls his miserable youth when he lost his only love due to his greed; the spirit of Christmas Present shows him the poor situation of Bob's family and how joyful life may be; and the spirit of Christmas Future shows his fate. Scrooge finds that life is good and time is too short and suddenly you are not there anymore, changing his behavior toward Christmas, Bob, his nephew and people in general.
U | 2h | Drama , Family , Fantasy | 1 December 1970</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/ikeq354kqx4q</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYzNmZDNhMjQtMDkwYy00MDRmLWJlNzAtMTI4MGU2OWM4ZmJiXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMjUyNDk2ODc@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,758,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYzNmZDNhMjQtMDkwYy00MDRmLWJlNzAtMTI4MGU2OWM4ZmJiXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMjUyNDk2ODc@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,758,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Scrooged</title>
<summary>Storyline
Francis Xavier Cross is a cynical, mean spirited television executive, he treats his loyal assistant with contempt. He just sacked a member of staff on Christmas Eve for simply disagreeing with him, and he's alienated himself from his brother who still insists on inviting Frank to Christmas dinner despite him refusing to go every year. However, Frank is forced to learn the true meaning of Christmas when he's visited by three ghosts.
PG | 1h 41min | Comedy , Drama , Fantasy | 25 November 1988</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/tmho87snb9f4</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BM2NlMDQzMDktNTMyZS00MjBjLWI0MmEtMzgzZDM2ZTVkNzE1XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTUyMzE4Mzg@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYWNlYzEyOWMtZmY5Ny00YWE4LTg0NzYtMTMyZGEwOWRkMjQxL2ltYWdlL2ltYWdlXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMjk3NTUyOTc@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Small Town Santa</title>
<summary>Storyline
On the eve of Christmas, Sheriff Rick Langston has lost his holiday spirit. But when he arrests a home intruder claiming to be Santa Claus, his world gets turned upside-down ! With the help of Lucy, the new girl in town, Santa helps show Rick that even when you feel that all is lost, love is all around you.
U | 1h 26min | Comedy | 27 October 2014</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/duta076upe13</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTQyMjQxMjI5MF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwODAxMDA3MjE@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTQyMjQxMjI5MF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwODAxMDA3MjE@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Stick Man</title>
<summary>Storyline
Stick Man, an animated twig, lives with his Stick Lady Love and their children in the family tree. Out one day for a jog he meets a little boy who throws him for his dog to fetch, some children who play Pooh-sticks with him and a swan who uses him to build a nest before being washed out to sea and onto a beach far from home. After several other humiliating encounters throughout the year he has an unexpected saviour in the form of Santa Claus who helps him to get home for Christmas with his family.
U | 27min | Animation , Family | TV Movie 25 December 2015</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/33otjn2svu5w</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNDQxMjAzMTYzNl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMDIwNDc1NzE@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNDQxMjAzMTYzNl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMDIwNDc1NzE@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Christmas Chronicles</title>
<summary>Storyline
The story of sister and brother, Kate and Teddy Pierce, whose Christmas Eve plan to catch Santa Claus on camera turns into an unexpected journey that most kids could only dream about.
1h 44min | Adventure , Comedy , Family | 22 November 2018</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/wik88pzsi7wg</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNTA3NjU3OTM2MV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNjQ2MzE1NjM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZGEyMjcwMWMtYThmYi00ZDJkLTljYTItYzFjNmIxZDQ2N2FkXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTExODIyNDM@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Christmas Dragon</title>
<summary>Storyline
A group of orphans goes on a journey to restore the lost magic and save Christmas.
PG | 1h 46min | Adventure , Drama , Fantasy | 7 November 2014</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/dkkqrx51ky4o</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTUwMDMxOTI0Ml5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNjk2NjI2OTE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,707,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNWRhMjJjZjgtMWY5Ni00MDE1LWIxMGYtZjc2M2UwYjQyZjY1L2ltYWdlXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTM4MTYwNQ@@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Christmas Switch</title>
<summary>Storyline
Eddie Bennett is a fast-talking, Three-card Monte dealer who has hustled the streets of New York City for the last 15 years. Eddie along with his friends, has mastered every scam there is until one day he is visited by a mysterious man who offers him an unusual proposition. He will give Eddie the chance to achieve eternal redemption for all the bad deeds he has done. The price is simple: he must transfer his spirit to a different body for three weeks. This way an aging, ailing Santa Claus, Sam, can use Eddie's body to play St. Nick for one more Christmas. Eddie thinks the man is nuts and beside, redemption is a sucker's bet. If he were to go through with the deal, he'd want a million dollars in cash. That's the pay off. The mysterious man snaps his fingers and a million dollars appears before a dumbfounded Eddie. "The choice is yours," says the man. "You can have the money or the pearly gates. That's up to you. All we want is your body for a few weeks." For one second Eddie hesitates and actually considers eternal redemption. He then comes to his senses. He takes the money of course. The terms are agreed upon and, at the stroke of midnight, Eddie finds himself in Sam's body and Sam in Eddie's. The next three weeks finds Sam bringing good cheer to kids throughout the city. Eddie, stuck in Sam's body, counts his time in bed just waiting to get paid. However, when Eddie follows Sam one day to a department store, he sees Sam, in his body, giving presents and cheer to the children. Eddie could never imagine himself doing that. But there he is, in the flesh, bringing joy to these children and their parents. Eddie starts to question the meaning of Christmas. Maybe it's not what he thinks it is: "Get what you can, when you can." Maybe there is something to this redemption thing. Moreover, Eddie meets Sam's daughter, Susan, and finds himself falling in love. Complications arise when Eddie's friends find out about the million dollar pay off and want part of the action. Eddie must overcome his greedy friends and allow Sam his final night on Christmas Eve. Through Eddie's wit and guile, he gives Sam that last night and finally finds the real meaning of Christmas the gambler's way.
1h 37min | Family | 9 November 2014</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/lyfti4c4sskr</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMGY0YmY1ZGUtN2IxOS00MGI4LTg1NDItYTM0ZTI2ZDQyOGQxXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNDgxMjMzMjU@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMGY0YmY1ZGUtN2IxOS00MGI4LTg1NDItYTM0ZTI2ZDQyOGQxXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNDgxMjMzMjU@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Flight Before Christmas</title>
<summary>Storyline
A reindeer boy named Niko dreams about flying like his father, whom he has never met. Despite constant mocking from others, he sneaks out of his home valley to take flying lessons from Julius, a flying squirrel.
G | 1h 20min | Animation , Adventure , Family | 10 October 2008</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/8nnzkp9mqkj7</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTg2OTI0OTUxM15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNzM3NzAwMg@@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjA2ZjdlZGEtMmYxMC00OTJjLTkwNDMtN2M3Y2Q3Zjc0ZmY0XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNDgyODgxNjE@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Gruffalo's Child</title>
<summary>Storyline
A little Gruffalo ignores her father's warnings and tiptoes out into the snow in search of the Big Bad Mouse.
U | 27min | Animation , Family | TV Movie 25 December 2011</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/gui47ffsilcbv</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTU2MDE0MTY5NF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMzA3NzA0MTE@._V1._CR0,43,342,456_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZWUwMDJjYmUtOTcyMC00ZmYzLThmYWItNjEwYjYzN2UzMjM4XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNDgyODgxNjE@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Holiday</title>
<summary>Storyline
In London, Iris Simpkins writes a wedding column in a newspaper and nurtures an unrequited love for her colleague Jasper Bloom. Near Christmas, she is informed that Jasper is engaged to marry another colleague, and her life turns upside down. In Los Angeles, the movie-trailers maker Amanda Woods has just split with her unfaithful boyfriend Ethan and wants to forget him. Through a house exchange website, Amanda impulsively swaps her mansion for Iris' cottage in Surrey for the holidays. While in Surrey, Amanda meets Iris' brother and book editor Graham and they fall in love with each other. Meanwhile, Iris meets her new next door neighbor the ninety year old screenplay writer Arthur, who helps her retrieve her self-esteem, and the film composer Miles, with whom she falls in love.
12A | 2h 18min | Comedy , Romance | 8 December 2006</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/s8azafjuw1ty</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTI1MDk4MzA2OF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTYwMjQ3NDc3._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTI1MDk4MzA2OF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTYwMjQ3NDc3._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Magic Reindeer</title>
<summary>Storyline
On Christmas Eve, Niko the young reindeer must find his little brother who has gone missing. But in order to save Christmas, it's going to take a lot of help from Niko's friends in order to save the day. While on his epic journey to save his brother, Niko learns the importance of friendship and family, in this heartwarming Holiday tale that all ages will enjoy.
G | 1h 19min | Animation , Adventure , Comedy | 12 October 2012</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/uy2r11ee34uq</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BODcwODcwNTE3MF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwODEyNjY0MTE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,687,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZjFmZmQ3M2MtYTU2Yi00MDFlLThkNjYtYTg4Y2Q4MjY2YTdkXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNDgyODgxNjE@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Man Who Invented Christmas</title>
<summary>Storyline
In 1843, the celebrated British novelist, Charles Dickens, is at a low point in his career with three flops behind him and his family expenses piling up at home. Determined to recover, Dickens decides to write a Christmas story and self-publish it in less than two months. As Dickens labors writing on such short notice, his estranged father and mother come to bunk with him. Still haunted by painful memories of his father ruining his childhood by his financial irresponsibly, Dickens develops a writer's block which seems to have no solution. As such, Dickens must face his personal demons epitomized through his characters, especially in his imagined conversations with Ebenezer Scrooge. Now with a looming deadline, Dickens struggles for inspiration against his frustrations and his characters' opinions in a literary challenge creating a classic tale that would define the essential soul of modern Christmas.
PG | 1h 44min | Biography, Comedy, Drama | 1 December 2017</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/arocvj14z9rm</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZDRjZWZlNjAtYjM1ZS00ZjAyLWE4MmEtNWVmNzZiNTYzOThjXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTMxODk2OTU@._V1_SY1000_SX675_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTYwMjk1MTUzM15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNDM2ODgwNDI@._V1_SX1327_CR0,0,1327,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Muppet Christmas Carol</title>
<summary>Storyline
A retelling of the classic Dickens tale of Ebenezer Scrooge, miser extraordinaire. He is held accountable for his dastardly ways during night-time visitations by the Ghosts of Christmas Past, Present, and future.
U | 1h 25min | Comedy , Drama , Family | 18 December 1992</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/2bgu53mcvhy1</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BN2Y0NWRkNWItZWEwNi00MDNlLWJmZDYtNTkwYzI5Nzg4MjVjXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTMxODk2OTU@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,676,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BN2Y0NWRkNWItZWEwNi00MDNlLWJmZDYtNTkwYzI5Nzg4MjVjXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTMxODk2OTU@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,676,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Nightmare Before Christmas</title>
<summary>Storyline
Jack Skellington, the pumpkin king of Halloween Town, is bored with doing the same thing every year for Halloween. One day he stumbles into Christmas Town, and is so taken with the idea of Christmas that he tries to get the resident bats, ghouls, and goblins of Halloween Town to help him put on Christmas instead of Halloween -- but alas, they can't get it quite right.
PG | 1h 16min | Animation , Family , Fantasy | 25 November 1994</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/siobrgd5c9w6</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNWE4OTNiM2ItMjY4Ni00ZTViLWFiZmEtZGEyNGY2ZmNlMzIyXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMDU5NDcxNw@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,666,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTQxNTY0NDE2Nl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMzg2ODMyMw@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,1618,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Nutcracker Sweet</title>
<summary>Storyline
It is Christmas Eve and the Silberhaus children are excited for the festivities to begin. Marie and Fritz are playing in the children's room when their godfather Drosselmayer arrives and presents them with an early Christmas gift, a Nutcracker. Marie witnesses a great battle between a vast army of toy soldiers led by the Nutcracker against a terrible platoon of mice commanded by the Mouse King. Follow Marie and Fritz's journey in the Kingdom of Dolls, through the Christmas Forest, past the Almond Milk Sea, and the Palace of the Marzipans.
U | 1h 20min | Animation | Video 9 November 2015</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/jkha0zvyiy6k</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTUxOTEyNjk0OF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMjA5ODA2NTE@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTUxOTEyNjk0OF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMjA5ODA2NTE@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Polar Express</title>
<summary>Storyline
This is the story of a young hero boy on Christmas Eve who boards on a powerful magical train that's headed to the North Pole and Santa Claus's home. What unfolds is an adventure which follows a doubting boy, who takes an extraordinary train ride to the North Pole; during this ride, he embarks on a journey of self-discovery which shows him that the wonder of life never fades for those who believe.
U | 1h 40min | Animation , Adventure , Comedy | 10 December 2004</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/97jqhbi9wdpz</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTM1NTU0NTE4MV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMTQ0MjEzMw@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,676,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTg0MTg1MjY1OF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNDMzNjgyMw@@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,783_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Santa Clause</title>
<summary>Storyline
Divorcee Scott Calvin is disgusted to learn that his ex and her husband have tried - and failed - to break it easy to their 6-year-old son Charlie that Santa isn't real. On Christmas Eve, Scott reads The Night Before Christmas... then receives an unexpected visitor on his roof. When he's startled by Scott's calling out and falls, the Santa impersonator disappears, leaving only an 8-reindeer sleigh and a suit with instructions to put it on if he's involved in an accident. Scott does, and is transported around the town dropping gifts through chimneys until he's taken to the North Pole and informed by a group who claim they're elves that he is now Santa. Charlie is proud of his dad's new job, though Scott's convinced it's a dream. Until his hair turns white, his beard refuses to stay shaved, he gains weight inexplicably, even for his sudden love of junk food... Now he's accepted it, there's just one problem: how to keep it secret from his disbelieving family?
U | 1h 37min | Comedy , Drama , Family | 8 December 1995</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/b4fv6pdlrygz</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYzI0ZGRiYTEtNGExYi00ZDI2LWExMjMtODMzNDZjMTVjOWMxXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTIzOTk5ODM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,675,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYzI0ZGRiYTEtNGExYi00ZDI2LWExMjMtODMzNDZjMTVjOWMxXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTIzOTk5ODM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,675,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Santa Clause 2</title>
<summary>Storyline
Scott Calvin has been Santa Claus for the past eight years, and his loyal elves consider him the best Santa ever. But Santa's got problems (he's even mysteriously losing weight) and things quickly go south when he finds out that his son, Charlie, has landed on this year's "naughty" list. Desperate to help his son, Scott heads back home, leaving a substitute Claus to watch over things at the Pole. But when the substitute institutes some strange redefinitions of naughty and nice, putting Christmas at risk, it's up to Scott to return with a new bag of magic to try to save Christmas.
U | 1h 44min | Comedy , Family , Fantasy | 29 November 2002</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/sjovwmae1ptv</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNjU0Njk5MTA2Nl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTYwODkzMzQ3._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMzkyMDEzNzU2NF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNzYzMjIyNw@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,1505,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Santa Clause 3: The Escape Clause</title>
<summary>Storyline
Now that Santa/Scott Calvin and Mrs. Claus/Carol Calvin have the North Pole running smoothly, the Counsel of Legendary Figures has called an emergency meeting on Christmas Eve! The evil Jack Frost has been making trouble, looking to take over the holiday! So he launches a plan to sabotage the toy factory and compel Scott to invoke the little-known Escape Clause and wish he'd never become Santa!
U | 1h 37min | Adventure , Comedy , Family | 24 November 2006</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/at2k40xjhxmd</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTI4ODQ4MzgzMl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwODc5NTUzMQ@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjA3MTkxODU5N15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNjczMjIyNw@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,1498,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Snowman</title>
<summary>Storyline
Wordless (save for the song "Walking in the Air") animated adventure about a young English boy who makes a snowman one Christmas Eve, only for it to come to life that night and take him on a magical adventure to the North Pole to meet Santa Claus.
U | 26min | Animation , Adventure , Family | TV Movie 26 December 1982</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/e57ic1np1md6</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMWM2MWMyYzYtNGJlMC00Mzk0LTk3NjEtYzY5OWQzOTY3ZmZhXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyODY0NzcxNw@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,730,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMWM2MWMyYzYtNGJlMC00Mzk0LTk3NjEtYzY5OWQzOTY3ZmZhXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyODY0NzcxNw@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,730,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Tom and Jerry: A Nutcracker Tale</title>
<summary>Storyline
Tom and his army of stray cats take over Jerry's magical kingdom of living toys. Chased by Tom and his cronies, Jerry must find the Toymaker and get help to win his kingdom back before sunrise when the window of opportunity closes.
U | 47min | Animation , Comedy , Family | Video 2 October 2007</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/qwb9t6qpcykc</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTQxNjM3NjM2OV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMjYxMjA2MDE@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjQxNTIxMjgxN15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwODg2NzAwNzE@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Thomas & Friends: Thomas' Christmas Carol</title>
<summary>Storyline
It's a winter wonderland on Sodor. Diesel gets a visit from some 'ghostly' Christmas engines, while Kevin enjoys playing in the snow until he's snowed under. Thomas and Cranky drop an important Christmas package and Henry faces off against an abominable snowman. Dash through the snow with Thomas and his friends as they deliver a jolly good time. Featuring the episodes: Diesel's Ghostly Christmas, Snow Place Like Home, A Cranky Christmas and The Beast of Sodor.
U | 55min | Animation , Family | Video 24 October 2016</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/nkxpl0ohov0n</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNjIyNjM5Nzc0OV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMDc5NjMwNzE@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNjIyNjM5Nzc0OV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMDc5NjMwNzE@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
<title>Wish for Christmas</title>
<summary>Storyline
When a high school senior finds out from her parents that she has to miss the town's winter dance to attend Christmas Eve service at church, she successfully wishes their faith away, bringing disastrous consequences to her family and community. To restore their faith, she is led through a series of Christmas adventures that change her heart and those around her.
U | 1h 29min | Drama , Family | 1 November 2016</summary>
<link>https://uptobox.com/gegg1ak3fp9b</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjEwODE4ODAyOV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMzUwNzg0MDI@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjEwODE4ODAyOV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMzUwNzg0MDI@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</item>